[Music]
[Música]
Listen to me, let's see what Eliv told you,
escúchame vamos a ver lo que te ha dicho
let's see if he gets it since
eliv no vamos a ver si pilla ya que
we're here today, what do you get? Because you get it
estamos hoy que pillas porque pilles por
everywhere. Oh no, it was something bad.
todos lados Ah no que ha sido algo malo
Besides, I don't know. I don't know. Let's see, today
además no lo sé No lo sé a ver hoy
you have a day to get it. Well, let's see
tienes un día de pillar pues vamos a ver
if you got it. Also, the
si que has pillado también que lo del
record thing could happen and he said, and if it happens, I
récord podía pasar y dijo y si ocurre
want to go up and congratulate you. He spoke to me on
quiero subir a felicitarte me habló por
WhatsApp days before, the
WhatsApp días antes pasó lo del tema del
record thing happened and that's it, we ended up fed up with the
récord y ya está que acabamos hasta los
record thing because
[__] del tema del récord porque
everyone was saying, the record,
estaba todo el mundo que lo el récord
the record, the record, the record,
que lo el récord que el récord que lo
and V on a podcast said that
del récord y V en un podcast dijeron que
you did it on purpose. How come I
tú lo hiciste a propósito Cómo que yo lo
did it on purpose, Gaman, I did it on
hice a propósito gaman que hice a
purpose. What, this, that I uploaded
propósito El qué el esto que yo lo subí
to Gref on a Willy Rex podcast,
a gref en un podcast de Willy Rex
gentlemen, Gref spoke to me days before
señores a mí gref me habló días antes de
this event, days before, he said, I'm going to go
este evento días antes me dijo ibai si
up there with you and
superas el récord quiero subir contigo a
congratulate you. That's what happened, I mean, he
felicitarte eso fue lo que ocurrió o sea
said, I want to, and this came from Gref, in
dijo quiero y esto salió de gref de
fact, uh, I mean, even the
hecho eh o sea ahí estarán hasta las
WhatsApp conversations will be there. I want to go
conversaciones de WhatsApp quiero subir
up there and  congratulate you and tell you
arriba y felicitarte y decirte
Congratulations I've surpassed myself and at this
Enhorabuena me superado y a mí este este
moment I felt
momento me dio una [__] vergüenza
incredibly ashamed but it's true that he wanted to
increíble pero es verdad que él quería
do it because he knew the record
hacerlo porque sabía que el récord se
could be broken But he said he wanted to
podía superar Pero él decía que quería
be like a gentleman and like to
quedar rollo en plan caballero y en plan
have good faith and say I'm going up and I
de de de tener buena fe y decir subo y
congratulate you and that's why this happened people
te felicito y ocurrió por esto gente una
something how the [ __ ] am I going to tell him gref
cosa cómo [__] voy a decirle yo gref
Get up up up get here you know what you're
Sube sube sube ponte aquí sabes qué te
breaking the record Take my [ __ ] I mean
supera el récord Toma mi [__] o sea por
please my God We're crazy please
favor Dios mío Estamos locos por favor
people we are we're crazy for God's sake I
gente estamos estamos locos por Dios
mean we're crazy in the head
santo o sea estamos locos de la cabeza
No man no [ __ ] yes gref goes up because it's
No hombre no [__] si gref sube porque
agreed and he wanted to go up and in
está pactado y él quería subir y de
fact it's more the proposal came from him I mean
hecho es más la propuesta salió de él o
he told me no no and by I go up because I
sea él me dijo no no y by subo yo porque
want to congratulate you in front of
quiero felicitarte delante de todo el
everyone I think that for the people it
mundo yo creo que también para la gente
was also a nice gesture to say damn Look gref you
fue un buen gesto decir [__] Mira gref
know he has the good heart to
sabes que que tiene el buen corazón de
say you go up and I congratulate you and I don't give a damn
decir tú sube y te felicito y me la pela
because it's true that back in the day do you
porque es verdad que en su día os
remember that we were always on the
acordáis que estábamos siempre con el
subject of the record if gref is going to be broken he will  They
tema del récord de si se va a superar a
were asking all the time are they going to
gref se lo preguntaban todo el rato van
beat your record that's it [ __ ] it
a superar tu récord ya está tomar por
the [ __ ] record of balls I'm
culo el [__] récord de los [__] estoy
fed up and that's it and it happened and period
hasta la [__] y ya está y pasó y punto
and well that's it well what are we going to
y pu pues ya está pues que le vamos a
do one day someone will beat my
hacer algún día a alguien superará mi
Twitch record I'm completely
récord de Twitch estoy completamente
sure and what am I going to do with that person well
seguro y qué voy a hacer con esa persona
if they're not from Spain or
pues como no sea de España o de
Latin America destroy them absolutely
latinoamérica destruirle absolutamente
no matter who they are I hope it's someone
no sea quien sea Ojalá que sea alguien
from Spain or Latin America Because if
de España o de latinoamérica Porque si
a guy found out that he's German
me supiera encima un tío que es alemán
then I'll say congratulations but I'm not
pues le diré congratulations pero no le
going to I mean it's not going to make any sense I'm going to
voy a O sea no va a tener sentido voy a
say congratulations and he's going to say
decir congratulations y va a decir él
okay and now thanks but this people
bueno y ya pues gracias pero esto gente
is going to happen and go it wasn't Willy it was the
va a ocurrir y va no fue Willy fue el
presenter man it would be weird if Willy
presentador hombre sería raro que Willy
said it like that yeah yes yes yes the
lo dijera así sí sí sí sí lo dijo el
presenter delox said it Yes yes Willy it would be weird
presentador delox Sí sí Willy sería raro
if he said it no no no people please
que lo dijera no no no gente por favor
for God's sake How is this going to happen
por Dios santo Cómo va a ocurrir esto
my God of my life please but
por Dios mío de mi vida por favor pero
this is true that it happened for [ __ ] I didn't
esto es verdad que ocurrió por [__] No
remember dude this scene dude eh
me acordaba macho de esta escena tío eh
[ __ ] gref uploaded here dude it was a
subió el [__] gref aquí tío fue un gesto
nice gesture really  it was a nice gesture and
bonito la verdad fue un gesto bonito y
here reben was applauding Bad
aquí reben aplaudiendo estaba que Bad
Bunny bad day to be delox eh u I
Bunny mal día para ser delox eh u yo me
take it as a victory eh I mean the
lo tomo como una victoria eh es decir el
mere fact the mere fact that they
mero hecho el mero hecho de que hayan
said delox in By's live for me
dicho delox en el directo de By para mí
is a small victory you know they don't
es una pequeña Victoria sabes de que no
say the name of all the podcasts that
dicen el nombre de todos los podcast que
are out there in fourth fifth sixth
están por ahí en cuarta quinta sexta
position to those they don't even mention them
posición a esos ni los mencionan
so for me it's something positive I
entonces para mí es algo positivo
also tell you if this wasn't public like
también te digo si esto no era público
he had never said that gref
en plan él nunca había dicho que gref
had the idea and me for things that I
había tenido la idea y yo por cosas que
know I'm not going to say because if not in the
sé que no voy a decir porque si no al
end I look like a spiteful person I accept The
final parezco un rencoroso yo acepto El
blow I accept the educational slap IV Don't
golpe acepto la colleja educativa IV No
worry I accept it but ivay I'm going to
te preocupes la acepto pero ivay voy a
say one thing that only he's going to understand
decir una cosa que solo él va a entender
If listen to this okay yv you understand that
Si Escucha esto vale yv tú entiendes que
if I know what happened in the I think they
si yo sé lo que pasó en los creo que
were the first slam the ones in
fueron los primeros eslan los de
Barcelona yes what I know what happened
Barcelona sí lo que yo sé lo que pasó
with you and gref in the first slam from
contigo y gref en los primeros slam de
there I thought eh that could be like
ahí yo pensé eh que eso podía ser como
well there wasn't as good a reaction
bueno que no había tan buena reacción
as maybe  the one who
como a lo mejor la que cara al público
tries to sell her personal opinion to the public has
se intenta vender opinión personal ha
spent time but what have you said
pasado tiempo a pero qu has soltado tú
Here let's see let's see see no but I'm not saying
Aquí que a ver a ver ver no pero no digo
[ __ ] to me I don't know I mean people
hostias a mí no me yo sé O sea la gente
talk let me explain So I can
habla me explico Entonces yo puedo
understand I can understand that he says
entender yo puedo entender que él diga
Look, well there was a good vibe
Mira pues ahí sí que había buen rollo
it was Gref's idea and it seems to me like a very
fue idea de gref y me parece una muy
good move on Gref's part because it's
buena jugada por parte de gref porque es
like trying to scratch something out of that clip
como intentar rascar algo de de ese clip
okay I saw it as like a lack
está bien yo lo vi como como una falta
of respect towards Gref if it was Gref's idea
de respeto hacia gref si fue ida de gref
then it's not a marketing move
entonces no es una jugada de marketing
by Gref Okay well I apologize for my my
de gref Okay pues pido disculpas por mi
for my comment because I was wrong
mi por mi comentario porque me equivoqué
but I had context in that case enough
pero yo tenía contexto en ese caso como
to think about it what the fact that Ivai uploaded
para pensarlo el qué lo de que el hecho
to Gref at that
de que subiera ivai a gref en ese
moment was like humiliating him
momento fue como como para humillarlo
like to say look no it wouldn't surprise me it would
como para decirle mira no no me
n't surprise me if
sorprendería no me sorprendería que lo
you had said it because any
hubieras dicho tú porque cualquier
person with two fingers of forehead and
persona con dos dos dedos de frente y
with a minimum of context would have thought that that's why
con un mínimo de contexto lo Hubiera
I thought it and I told
pensado por eso lo pensé yo y se lo dije
Willy Willy laughed or something like that
a Willy Willy se rió o algo así en plan
Well me what  I know I'm not getting involved you know you didn't
de Bueno yo que sé no me meto sabes no
put it in the teaser Even in the
lo pusiste en el teaser Incluso en el
tier inus that in the teer I did
tier inus eso en el teer yo en el teaser
n't put it in the teaser that yes in the teaser in the
no lo puse eso si en el teaser en el
teaser Well I don't know if you or Willy were saying it
teaser Bueno no sé si lo decías tú o
but in the teaser if you put the
Willy pero en el teaser si pones la
part that says ah no yes Don where Gref
parte que dice ah no sí Don donde gref
says nobody gets along nobody gets along with
dice nadie se lleva nadie se lleva con
with Gref or something like that We did put that in
con gref o algo así Eso sí lo pusimos en
the teaser but come on No but the thing about him
el teaser pero vamos No pero lo de que
uploading it he uploaded it at the party to
lo sube lo subió en la velada para
humiliate him and such it may be I don't
humillarlo y tal puede ser no lo
remember the truth is it's been a while
recuerdo la verdad tiene ya un tiempo
but come on whatever it is or not in the
pero vamos sea como sea est o no en el
teaser it's in the podcast it's a
teaser está en el podcast es un
comment that I say yes or yes 100%
comentario que sí o sí suelto yo 100%
but come on eh I'm telling you because I prefer to
pero vamos eh Te digo yo porque prefiero
receive one and not receive two Okay
recibir una y no recibir dos Vale
then I'm not going to talk too much but
entonces no voy a hablar de más pero
but but I'm telling you I think I've had
pero pero te digo yo creo
enough status to know
suficientemente estado como para saber
that people maybe he doesn't know that I
que la gente quizá él no sabe que yo
'm very well connected but I have a
estoy muy bien conectado pero yo tengo
lot of context Okay and from people very
mucho contexto Vale y de gente muy
close to him that I really know that the
cercana a él que realmente yo sé que la
reaction wasn't good then that now it
reacción no era buena entonces que ahora
's good hopefully dude it is  I'm telling you
es buena ojal tío es que te lo digo en
seriously I hope everyone gets along
serio Ojalá todo el mundo se lleve bien
and it's all hugs and the
y todo sean abrazos y de esto la
reality is that people talk and it's not like that you
realidad es que la gente habla y no es
know then I hope I hope they
así sabes entonces Ojalá ojalá que se
get along then at the end of the day I'm
lleven bien entonces yo al final del día
telling you I also understand that
ya te digo yo entiendo también que
when they give him that comment what is
cuando le dan ese comentario qué va a
IV going to say is he going to say yes well the the the
decir IV va a decir sí pues el el el
Random this one from delox who calls me
Random este de delox que me llama
presenter because and he goes and sees my spot in
presentador porque y va y ve mi spot por
case someone suddenly no the presenter
si alguien de repente no el presentador
has called you the people in the chat he has
te lo ha llamado la gente del chat él ha
said delox because they also put it in
dicho delox porque también lo ponían en
the chat that I have seen it Oh okay they
el chat que lo he visto Ah vale lo
put it I have looked at it he is checking the
ponían lo he mirado est revisando el
chat But he gets a little crazy but
chat Pero él se hace un poco loco pero
he knows what my name you are
él sabe cómo me llamo me me estás
telling me that and he goes and doesn't know that I exist
diciendo que y va y no sabe que existo
dude if the tiktok when he is [ __ ]
cabrón si los tiktok cuando está [__]
he must plug them two by two
se los debe enchufar de dos en dos
because spam let's go a lot of tiktok he
porque spame vamos un montón de tiktok
must have me let's go his face
debe tenerme vamos la cara me la
recognizes me for sure what's going on That obviously
reconoce seguro qué pasa Que obviamente
the guy is not going to tell you in this case and And
el tío no te va a decir en este caso y Y
more if it's true that gref proposed to him he has let
más si es cierto que gref le propuso
's go the perfect excuse to
tiene vamos la excusa perfecta para
justify himself  but it's that Put it that it wasn't like that
justificarse pero es que Ponle que no
you think he's going to
que no fuera así tú crees que él te va a
tell you Ah well the truth is if I uploaded it to
decir Ah pues la verdad si lo subí para
humiliate him he's not going to tell you come on
humillarlo no te lo va a decir en vamos
but neither crazy nor crazy Don't you see that for
pero ni loco ni loco No ves que por
example I have avoided talking about the Cos subject
ejemplo he evitado hablar del tema Cos
because he's going to talk about what interests him what he's not
porque va a hablar de lo que le interesa
going to talk about but it's
de lo que no no va a hablar pero es que
logical in the end it's a company it's not
es lógico al final es una empresa no es
just his opinion I'm not taking it you're not
solo su opinión Yo no me lo tomo no te
going to believe what I'm going to tell you
lo vas a creer lo que te voy a decir
now tell me audio of 3 minutes yes
ahora dime audio de de 3 minutos sí
come on come on I'm already laughing yes yes
venga va ya me descojono que sí que sí
audio div audio divy audio divy chat
audio div audio divy audio divy chat
press the like button guys come on come on live come on
pulsar el botón de like cabres que vaya
live today audio
vaya directo vaya directo hoy audio
audio don't go no audio div of 3
audio no te vayas no audio div de 3
minutes kid like kid
minutos chaval dadle like chaval dle
like the live eh this live is wow
like al directo eh este directo váy tela
how are we today what a little program today eh
como estamos hoy vaya programita hoy eh
audio gone everywhere come on come on pay
audio andado por todos lados venga va
attention no but listen to me eh what is
atento no pero escúchame eh qué está
made with Artificial Intelligence no no
hecho con Inteligencia artificial no no
but if you know ivai man yes but
pero que si sabe ivai hombre si pero
apart ivai [ __ ] [ __ ] Well go on
aparte ivai [__] [__] Pues anda que
come on he hasn't sent me audios while I'm here live message I'm watching you Javi Shut up I don't know what I don't know how much some thing I know I'm going I'll tell you one thing before Put it the audio is real and it's not bait if it goes in the audio it allows me to
bait si vai en el audio me permite
explain what I know I say it is not a
explicar lo que sé yo lo digo no es
bluff Eh I have no problem
ningún farol Eh no tengo ningún problema
but I of him I think it's not good for me to
pero yo de él Creo que no es bueno que
say it but let's see if he doesn't allow you
lo diga pero a ver si no te lo permite
also comment on it no no because it's something
también coméntalo no no porque es algo
personal and and I've already received a hit
personal y y ya he recibido una [__]
for telling things that I didn't know I
por contar cosas que no sabía que no
couldn't already has a hot face what
podía ya tiene la cara calientita queé
more do you give Then I'm already going to
más das Entonces yo ya voy caliente a
sleep horny I don't want more I don't want it go go We put it we put it we
dormir No quiero más no quiero va va Lo
put it let's
ponemos lo ponemos lo ponemos a
see
ver
a little strange a little strange ivay a little
un poco raro un poco raro ivay un poco
strange the truth a little strange that you
raro la verdad un poco raro que te has
looked for an audio troll [ __ ] a joke
buscado un audio troll cabrón una broma
yo putti let's be the poll would already have been already
yo putti vamos ser la poll sería ya
the [ __ ] we have
hubiera sido ya la [__] tenemos
prepared a clip for you from Ari
preparado un clip para ti de Ari
Gameplay and Juan Guarnizo but this guy
Gameplay y Juan guarnizo pero este tío
is stupid this is your idol this is
es tonto este es vuestro ídolo este es
your idol but How to be a host by  that's
vuestro ídolo pero Cómo ser [__] por
if someone was on the subway eh That's
esito si iba alguien en el metro eh Por
why someone was there don't remove the like
esito iba algu alguen no quitéis los lik
no don't remove the like eh Don't remove the
no no quitéis los lik eh No quitéis los
like give it a like give it a like I had it
lik dadle al like dle al like lo tenía
at maximum Okay, I'm sorry, know what you
al máximo Bueno pues lo siento sabé lo
're seeing
que estáis viendo
[Music]
[Música]
okay
vale